(Just For Love)
(그냥 사랑을 위해)
(Episode 4)
(4화)
I just heard something.
방금 뭔가를 들었습니다.
Actually Xu Yu Ling went to interview Fang Shi Yan yesterday.
사실 Xu Yu Ling은 어제 Fang Shi Yan을 인터뷰하러 갔습니다.
A moment. Why are you so calm?
순간. 왜 그렇게 침착합니까?
I went to the editor's office this morning…
오늘 아침에 편집실 에 갔는데 …
and saw Xu Yu Ling hand over the draft.
Xu Yu Ling이 초안을 넘겨주는 것을 보았습니다 .
I was thinking…
나는 생각하고 있었다…
no interview task these two days either.
이틀 동안에도 인터뷰 작업이 없습니다 .
Why did he submit the draft?
그가 초안을 제출한 이유는 무엇입니까?
Then, while I was in the pantry earlier,
그러다가 아까 식료품 저장실에 있었을 때,
I heard that he actually went to interview Fang Shi Yan.
그가 실제로 Fang Shi Yan을 인터뷰하러 갔다고 들었습니다 .
You know what's even more annoying?
더 짜증나는 게 뭔지 아세요 ?
I've read your interview outline, haven't I?
나는 당신의 면접 개요를 읽었습니다 , 그렇죠?
He literally copied your entire interview outline.
그는 말 그대로 전체 인터뷰 개요를 복사했습니다.
What do you think all this is?
이 모든 것이 무엇이라고 생각하시나요?
For real.
진짜.
Tuan Shi.
투안시.
Did I say it wrong?
내가 잘못 말했나요?
I did not follow the framework and interviewed question after question,
프레임워크를 따르지 않고 질문을 계속해서 인터뷰했는데,
but Shi Yan must have known it was the same outline of the interview.
하지만 Shi Yan은 그것이 인터뷰의 개요와 동일 하다는 것을 알았을 것입니다 .
And, he answered the same question twice.
그리고 그는 같은 질문에 두 번이나 대답했습니다.
Xu Yu Ling memang penipu.
Xu Yu Ling memang penipu.
Yu Ling, you are so great.
Yu Ling, 당신은 정말 대단해요.
You can interview Shi Yan.
Shi Yan을 인터뷰할 수 있습니다.
Yes, Yu Ling, you are really great.
응, Yu Ling, 당신은 정말 대단해요.
Just a small thing. You two, work hard.
아주 작은 일이에요. 두 분, 열심히 하세요.
- Did you hear that? - Loud and clear.
- 들었어? - 크고 명확합니다.
The interview went awry and the transcript of the interview was stolen.
인터뷰가 잘못되었고 인터뷰 녹취록이 도난당했습니다.
I was also played while riding a horse.
말을 타면서 놀기도 했어요 .
Oh God.
오 맙소사.
How many embarrassing things have I done in front of him?
그 사람 앞에서 내가 얼마나 부끄러운 짓을 했나요?
Actually, this Shi Yan was quite good.
사실 이번 Shi Yan은 꽤 좋았습니다.
He was a busy man, but he still received two interviews.
그는 바쁜 사람이었지만 여전히 두 번의 인터뷰를 받았습니다.
He seems to be quite patient with you.
그 사람은 당신에게 꽤 인내심을 갖고 있는 것 같아요 .
If you want to say that the people are quite good.
사람들이 꽤 좋다고 말하고 싶다면 .
He holds a grudge.
그는 원한을 품고 있습니다.
His mood changes quickly.
그의 기분은 빠르게 변합니다.
He also likes to see people doing embarrassing things.
그는 또한 사람들이 당황스러운 일을 하는 것을 보는 것을 좋아합니다 .
But, if you want to say that the person is not good.
하지만 그 사람이 좋지 않다고 말하고 싶다면 .
He doesn't seem to have any malicious intent.
악의적인 의도는 없는 것 같습니다.
But, when interviewed, you don't know what he is thinking.
하지만 인터뷰를 하면 그가 무슨 생각을 하는지 알 수 없습니다.
He is a great actor.
그는 훌륭한 배우입니다.
I do not understand this man.
나는 이 사람을 이해하지 못한다.
Mr. Shi. Marketing and Finance Department …
시 씨. 마케팅 및 재무 부서…
just released the Le'an assessment report.
방금 Le'an 평가 보고서를 발표했습니다.
From what we can see now, there is still room for negotiation.
지금 볼 수 있듯이 아직 협상의 여지가 남아 있습니다.
But, you really consider to…
하지만, 당신은 정말로 다음을 고려하고 있습니다…
Besides that,
그 외에도
where did they get so much money all of a sudden?
갑자기 그 많은 돈이 어디서 났나 ?
There will always be someone…
항상 누군가가있을 것입니다…
who is willing to do something profitable.
이익이 되는 일을 기꺼이 하는 사람 .
Shu Yi, long time no see.
슈이님, 오랜만이군요.
Where are you going? I'll give you a ride.
어디 가세요? 내가 태워다 줄게.
Thanks, no need.
고마워요. 그럴 필요 없어요.
I was alone in the car.
나는 차에 혼자 있었다.
This car was bought for me by Le Zhi.
이 차는 Le Zhi가 나를 위해 구입했습니다 .
I will be working at Mingyu in two days.
저는 이틀 뒤에 민규에서 일하게 됩니다 .
If you like driving so much, why don't you become a driver?
운전을 그토록 좋아한다면 운전기사가 되어 보는 것은 어떨까요?
Who's this?
이 사람 누구야?
He has a very nice car.
그는 아주 좋은 차를 갖고 있어요.
Why did he just gift you a Mercedes worth 300,000?
왜 그는 당신에게 30만 달러 상당의 메르세데스를 선물했습니까?
And, you still have to wait a few days before you can go to work?
그리고 아직도 출근하려면 며칠 기다려야 하나요 ?
For something that uncle can achieve with one sentence,
삼촌이 한 문장으로 이룰 수 있는 일에 대해 ,
why do you have to go through so many interviews before you can get in?
왜 입사하기 전에 그렇게 많은 인터뷰를 거쳐야 합니까 ?
It feels like you'd better be quick and work hard as a driver.
운전자로서 빠르고 열심히 일하는 것이 좋을 것 같습니다 .
Don't stop here and get busy.
여기서 멈추지 말고 바쁘게 지내십시오.
Shan Shan!
샨샨!
You are really good at scolding people.
당신은 사람을 꾸짖는 데 정말 능숙해요 .
That was a great relief.
정말 큰 위안이 되었습니다.
With his mentality,
그의 사고방식으로,
he still dreams of riding in the car that is there...
그는 아직도 거기 있는 차를 타는 꿈을 꿉니다...
registration plate with repeating digits.
반복되는 숫자가 있는 등록판 .
He looked down on Shi Yan too much,
그는 Shi Yan을 너무 무시했고,
and too sure of myself.
그리고 나 자신에 대해 너무 확신해요.
Let him come.
그를 오게 해주세요.
Ms. Zheng might prefer this car.
Zheng 씨는 이 차를 더 좋아할 것 같아요.
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
Some people can change their car easily,
어떤 사람들은 쉽게 차를 바꿀 수 있지만,
but I work hard...
하지만 난 열심히 일해..
only to have my interview outline stolen and my interview fail.
내 인터뷰 개요가 도난 당하고 인터뷰가 실패했습니다.
Stop saying sad things.
슬픈 말은 그만하세요 .
With your face that can overthrow a kingdom...
왕국을 무너뜨릴 수 있는 얼굴로 ...
and destroy a country,
나라를 멸망시키고,
I, as a woman, can't refuse it.
여자로서 거절할 수가 없어요.
What man can turn you down?
어떤 남자가 당신을 거절할 수 있나요?
Even though my face looks like what you said,
네 말대로 내 얼굴은 똑같아 보여도
i'm still being played…
난 아직도 놀고 있는 중이야…
and left alone in the car.
그리고 차에 혼자 남겨졌습니다.
I helped you make an appointment with Situ Yi.
Situ Yi와의 약속을 도와드렸습니다 .
You know how hard it is to make a date with him now?
지금 그 사람과 데이트하기 가 얼마나 힘든지 알아요 ?
Luckily, we had some connections when we were in school.
다행스럽게도 우리는 학교에 다닐 때 몇 가지 인연이 있었습니다 .
We share our experiences in love,
우리는 사랑에 대한 경험을 공유합니다 .
and I also lent her clothes for appointments.
그리고 나는 약속을 위해 그녀에게 옷을 빌려주기도 했습니다.
We have some influence relationships.
우리는 영향력 있는 관계를 갖고 있습니다.
Otherwise, you won't be able to meet him.
그렇지 않으면 그 사람을 만날 수 없습니다.
Shan Shan, thank you.
샨샨, 고마워요.
That's why I bought you this delicious meal, okay?
그래서 내가 너한테 맛있는 음식을 사준 거야, 알았지?
Honestly, darling,
솔직히 말해서, 자기야,
Even I, as a woman, can't reject you with that expression.
나조차도 여자로서 그런 표정으로 너를 거부할 수는 없다.
So, why does Shi Yan treat you like that?
그럼 Shi Yan은 왜 당신을 그렇게 대합니까?
Or, should I say,
아니면, 이렇게 말해야 할까요?
all men like to sell expensive?
남자들은 다 비싸게 팔고 싶어?
So, they talk like they don't like it, and act like real men.
그래서 싫은 척 말하고, 진짜 남자처럼 행동한다.
What matters now is not one man's strategy,
지금 중요한 것은 한 사람의 전략이 아니라,
but to retake my headline coverage.
하지만 내 헤드라인 보도를 다시 취재하려고요.
You are so persistent about covering this year's headlines.
당신은 올해의 헤드라인을 다루려고 끈질기게 노력하고 있습니다 .
I don't want to compete for headline coverage. I just want to…
나는 헤드라인 보도를 위해 경쟁하고 싶지 않습니다 . 나는 그저 원할 뿐이야…
"Prove me that I have the ability to be promoted..."
"내가 승진할 능력이 있다는 걸 증명해봐라..."
"to write for digital magazines."
" 디지털 잡지에 글을 쓰려고요."
You want to write for a digital magazine with a new perspective…
새로운 관점으로 디지털 매거진 에 글을 쓰고 싶다 …
which speaks for the common financial reader,
이는 일반적인 금융 독자를 대변하는 것입니다.
which is different from paper magazines, right?
종이잡지 랑은 다르죠 ?
I've heard you say that many times .
나는 당신이 그렇게 말하는 것을 여러 번 들었습니다.
But, from an outsider's perspective,
하지만 외부인의 입장에서 보면,
you're still competing for headline coverage, aren't you?
당신은 여전히 ​​헤드라인 보도를 위해 경쟁하고 있는 거죠, 그렇죠?
Actually,
실제로,
wouldn't it be great to be a deputy author?
부작가가 되면 좋지 않을까요 ?
It might be great to be a deputy author,
부작가로 활동하면 좋을 것 같은데 ,
but that's not really my goal.
하지만 그건 내 목표가 아니야.
Embracing change and writing for digital magazines…
변화를 수용하고 디지털 매거진을 위한 글쓰기…
is my professional ideal.
내 직업적 이상입니다.
you see,
알다시피,
when I interviewed Shi Yan,
내가 Shi Yan을 인터뷰했을 때,
he changed the interview time immediately and we were surprised.
바로 인터뷰 시간을 바꿔서 우리도 놀랐다.
But, writing for a digital magazine won't be like that.
하지만 디지털 매거진에 글을 쓰는 것은 그렇지 않습니다.
We can maintain the timeliness of the news,
우리는 뉴스의 적시성을 유지할 수 있습니다 .
and there are various ways of publication.
그리고 출판의 방법도 다양합니다.
Just send the link and we can share it.
링크를 보내주시면 공유해 드리겠습니다.
This has become a new reading habit of people nowadays.
이것이 요즘 사람들의 새로운 독서 습관이 되었습니다 .
And, there are also various formats we can choose from…
그리고 선택할 수 있는 형식도 다양합니다…
to convey to the reader.
독자에게 전달하기 위해.
So, I will not give up.
그래서 나는 포기하지 않을 것이다.
I have already planned a special coverage…
이미 특별 취재를 계획했는데…
to put in a digital magazine.
디지털 매거진에 실리려고요.
If that can be realized,
그것이 실현될 수 있다면,
so I will be one step closer to my goal.
그래서 목표에 한걸음 더 다가가겠습니다 .
Mr. Shi, I'm sorry.
시 선생님, 죄송합니다.
It's time to go back and I'm still bothering you.
이제 돌아갈 시간인데 아직도 너를 괴롭히고 있구나.
It's fine.
괜찮아.
Let's drink first.
먼저 마시자.
Is something important happening?
뭔가 중요한 일이 일어나고 있나요?
After we talk about the duration of the day,
하루의 지속 시간에 대해 이야기한 후,
I always think what you say,
나는 항상 당신이 말하는 것을 생각합니다.
and discuss it with the team.
그리고 팀과 함께 논의해보세요.
We don't want to lose a great visionary like you.
우리는 당신과 같은 위대한 선지자를 잃고 싶지 않습니다 .
So, I came this time…
그래서 이번에 왔는데...
to talk to you again about the investment amount.
투자금액에 대해 다시 말씀드리려고 합니다 .
Yes.
예.
I am so glad that you came looking for me at this time.
이 시간에 저를 찾으러 와주셔서 너무 기뻐요 .
But, Mr. Chen, please give me some time.
하지만 첸 씨, 시간을 좀 주세요.
I understand that.
나는 이해.
Renegotiation will definitely take some time.
재협상에는 확실히 시간이 걸릴 것입니다.
But,
하지만,
I have some pressure on my side.
나는 내 편에 약간의 압력을 가하고 있습니다.
I'm glad you reconsidered my suggestion.
내 제안을 다시 생각해 주셔서 기뻐요 .
I will give you an answer as soon as possible.
최대한 빨리 답변 해 드리겠습니다 .
Okay.
좋아요.
If you follow what you say,
그 말대로 따라하면,
you and Xu Yu Ling use the same skeleton,
당신과 Xu Yu Ling은 같은 뼈대를 사용합니다.
very difficult to know who won or lost,
누가 이겼는지, 졌는지 알기가 매우 어렵습니다 .
unless you have a way to get new content.
새로운 콘텐츠를 얻을 수 있는 방법이 없다면 말이죠 .
You are right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
But, I have to meet him for new content.
하지만 새로운 콘텐츠를 위해서는 그를 만나야 해요 .
Look for opportunities.
기회를 찾으십시오.
You two rode horses together yesterday.
어제 두 사람은 함께 말을 탔습니다 .
That counts as a bit of a personal connection, right?
그것은 약간의 개인적인 관계로 간주됩니다. 그렇죠?
I don't even have his WeChat,
나는 그 사람의 위챗도 갖고 있지 않아요.
how can that be called a personal relationship?
그걸 어떻게 개인적인 관계라고 할 수 있나요?
After all, he is very strange.
결국 그는 매우 이상합니다.
Does it matter if he's weird or not?
그 사람이 이상한지 아닌지가 중요한가요 ?
You need to be clear with your goals, Zheng Shu Yi.
목표를 분명히 해야 해요 , Zheng Shu Yi.
You're not just fighting for headline coverage.
당신은 단지 헤드라인 보도를 위해 싸우는 것이 아닙니다 .
You fight so that one day,
당신은 언젠가 그렇게 싸우고 있습니다 .
you can destroy that useless man…
그 쓸모없는 사람을 파괴하면 돼 …
and the girl who stole your interview.
그리고 당신의 인터뷰를 훔친 그 소녀 .
You also fight to upgrade the digital magazine…
당신은 또한 디지털 매거진을 업그레이드하기 위해 싸우고 있습니다…
long awaited.
오래 기다렸습니다.
The goods have been sent to you via express order.
상품은 빠른 주문을 통해 귀하에게 발송되었습니다 .
Don't forget to check.
확인하는 것을 잊지 마세요.
- Who's he? - Someone who is boring.
- 그 사람은 누구죠? - 지루한 사람.
Another man has fallen at your feet.
또 다른 사람이 당신의 발 앞에 쓰러졌습니다.
So many people are chasing you.
정말 많은 사람들이 당신을 쫓고 있습니다.
None you like?
마음에 드는 사람은 없나요?
You do not understand.
당신은 이해하지 않는다.
My principle is…
내 원칙은…
didn't refuse, didn't explain, didn't appeal.
거절하지도, 설명하지도, 항소하지도 않았다.
After all, he wants to trick me with such basic tricks?
결국 그는 그런 기본적인 속임수로 나를 속이고 싶습니까?
He looks down on me, doesn't he?
그 사람은 나를 무시하는 것 같죠?
What trick?
무슨 트릭?
Use excuses to help me fix something…
뭔가를 고치는 데 도움을 주기 위해 변명을 사용하세요 …
and deliberately left something at my house,
그리고 일부러 집에 물건을 두고 왔는데요.
in order to create an opportunity to meet like this.
이렇게 만날 수 있는 기회를 만들기 위해 .
Such a cheap trick, and people still use it today.
아주 값싼 방법이고, 사람들은 오늘날에도 여전히 그것을 사용하고 있습니다.
Speaking of which,
말하자면,
I also have something left in Shi Yan there.
나도 거기 Shi Yan에 남은 것이 있습니다.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
왜 더 일찍 말하지 않았나요?
That's a great opportunity to meet.
만날 수 있는 좋은 기회 입니다 .
Helo.
헬리콥터.
Tuan Shi.
투안시.
Miss Zheng Shu Yi from Financial Introduction is looking for you.
Financial Introduction 의 Zheng Shu Yi 선생님이 당신을 찾고 있습니다.
Helo?
헬리콥터?
Helo, Tuan Shi.
안녕하세요, 투안시.
I think my earrings fell in your car.
내 귀걸이가 당신 차에 떨어진 것 같아요 .
Did you see it?
당신은 그것을 볼 않았다?
I don't see.
모르겠어요.
Earrings are very important to me.
귀걸이는 나에게 매우 중요합니다.
Can you search again?
다시 검색할 수 있나요?
How important is it?
얼마나 중요합니까?
More important than my life.
내 목숨보다 더 중요해요.
It is important because…
중요한 이유는…
it was left to my mother by my grandmother,
할머니가 어머니에게 남겨주신 거예요 .
and my mother gave it to me.
그리고 어머니가 그것을 나에게 주셨습니다.
It's a family heirloom...
가문의 유산이군요...
and my wedding present.
그리고 내 결혼 선물.
I plan to wear it at my future wedding.
앞으로 결혼식 때 입을 예정이에요 .
When I saw it, I remembered my grandmother.
그걸 보니 할머니가 생각나더군요.
I haven't seen him in a long time.
나는 그를 오랫동안 보지 못했습니다.
My grandmother wrapped it in a scarf with six layers,
할머니가 6겹으로 된 스카프로 감싸주셨는데,
and keep it for years.
수년 동안 보관하십시오 .
Usually, I don't take it out to wear.
보통 은 꺼내서 입지 않아요 .
So, why are you willing to use it this time?
그렇다면 이번에는 왜 기꺼이 사용하시겠습니까?
This is because…
이 때문입니다…
This is because it is a very valuable heirloom .
매우 귀중한 가보이기 때문입니다.
Only worthy of the important moment when I interview you.
내가 당신을 인터뷰하는 중요한 순간에만 합당합니다 .
I have seen it.
나는 그것을 보았다.
Your wedding gift is made of plastic.
당신의 결혼 선물은 플라스틱으로 만들어졌습니다.
About that…
그것에 대해…
My ancestors were poor and life was very difficult.
나의 조상은 가난했고 생활이 매우 어려웠습니다.
They are farmers.
그들은 농부입니다.
They don't see much of the world.
그들은 세상의 많은 것을 보지 못합니다.
Although it is made of plastic,
플라스틱으로 만들어졌지만 ,
but it was the most valuable item in our family at that time.
하지만 그것은 당시 우리 가족에게 가장 귀중한 물건이었습니다 .
Send it to him.
그에게 보내세요.
Miss Zheng, when do you need it?
Miss Zheng, 언제 필요하세요?
As soon as possible. I can't sleep without seeing it.
최대한 빨리. 그것을 보지 않고는 잠을 잘 수 없습니다 .
Well, I'll send it to you.
글쎄요, 제가 보내드릴게요.
So.
그래서.
I don't want to trouble you.
나는 당신을 괴롭히고 싶지 않습니다.
I'll go get it myself.
제가 직접 가서 가져오겠습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Shu Yi, what are you thinking?
슈이, 무슨 생각을 하는 거야?
You met Shi Yan with a pair of plastic earrings?
플라스틱 귀걸이를 하고 시얀을 만났나요 ?
Why plastic?
왜 플라스틱인가?
Plastic is one of man's greatest inventions.
플라스틱은 인류의 가장 위대한 발명품 중 하나입니다 .
Plastic has improved human life.
플라스틱은 인간의 삶을 향상시켰습니다 .
Why look down on plastic?
왜 플라스틱을 무시합니까?
What are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
You've embarrassed yourself like this,
당신 은 이렇게 부끄러워했어요 .
and Shi Yan didn't put your phone down.
그리고 Shi Yan은 전화기를 내려놓지 않았습니다.
He also wants to send it to you.
그는 또한 그것을 당신에게 보내고 싶어합니다.
He must be interested in you.
그 사람이 당신에게 관심이 있는 게 틀림없어요.
Bogang Yunwan?
보강윤완?
For a residential area with this price,
이 가격의 주거 지역의 경우 ,
no need to even think to know that this is the address of Shi Yan's residence.
이것이 Shi Yan의 거주지 주소라는 것을 알 필요조차 없습니다 .
Is he so honest?
그 사람이 그렇게 솔직한가?
This is called having no feelings for you?
이걸 당신에 대한 감정이 없다고 하는 건가요?
How could it be…
어떻게 그럴수있어…
So…
그래서…
Just leave me alone in the lobby and go.
그냥 로비에 혼자 두고 가세요.
He doesn't even want to eat with me.
그 사람은 나와 함께 식사할 생각도 없어요.
You throw the bait,
미끼를 던지면,
and he immediately sent you the address.
그리고 그는 즉시 당신에게 주소를 보냈습니다.
Is he so impatient?
그 사람이 그렇게 참을성이 없나요?
He is not usually impatient.
그는 보통 참을성이 없습니다 .
So, there's only one meaning to this.
그러므로 이것에는 오직 하나의 의미가 있습니다.
All man are the same.
모든 사람은 동일합니다.
I'm telling you, in this situation, you shouldn't go.
이런 상황에서는 가지 말아야 한다고 말씀드리고 싶습니다 .
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Just take action that will definitely work, understand?
확실히 효과가 있는 조치를 취하세요 . 이해하셨나요?
I understand.
이해합니다.
But, not this time.
하지만 이번에는 그렇지 않습니다.
I have a plan to discuss with Shi Yan.
Shi Yan과 논의 할 계획이 있습니다 .
What plan?
무슨 계획?
Uncle,
삼촌,
why are you back?
왜 돌아왔어?
Shouldn't you meet Guan Ji?
Guan Ji를 만나면 안 되나요 ?
Didn't you say not to call him Guan Ji?
관지라고 부르지 말라고 하지 않았나요 ?
Guan Ji said call him Guan Ji.
Guan Ji는 그를 Guan Ji라고 부르라고 말했습니다.
Uncle hasn't told me why he suddenly came back tonight.
삼촌은 오늘 밤 갑자기 왜 돌아왔는지 나에게 말하지 않았습니다 .
This is my house.
이 내 집.
If you don't want to see me, go back and live with your grandfather.
나 보기 싫으면 돌아가서 할아버지 집에서 살아라.
I will pack my things.
나는 내 물건을 포장할 것이다.
Sit in the room. Don't go out unless I tell you to.
방에 앉으세요. 내가 지시하지 않는 한 나가지 마세요.
(Bogang Yunwan)
(보강윤완)
- Thank You. - You're welcome.
- 감사합니다. - 천만에요.
Mr. Shi, I am here to take something.
시 선생님, 저는 뭔가를 가져오러 왔습니다.
Mr. Shi, are you also interested in Song Le Lan?
Shi씨, Song Le Lan에도 관심이 있으신가요 ?
One coincidence.
우연의 일치 하나.
I also really like it. I have all his albums.
나도 정말 좋아해요. 나는 그의 모든 앨범을 가지고 있습니다.
Which of his songs do you like the most?
그의 노래 중 어떤 노래를 가장 좋아하나요?
Why did you suddenly cancel the appointment?
왜 갑자기 약속을 취소 했어요 ?
Chen Sheng said you are working,
Chen Sheng이 당신이 일하고 있다고 말했습니다.
but Yue said you are at home.
그런데 Yue가 당신이 집에 있다고 했어요.
So, that must not be for work.
그러니 업무용이 아니어야 합니다.
Speak up. Maybe you're in love with someone?
발언. 어쩌면 당신은 누군가와 사랑에 빠졌습니까?
You haven't been in a relationship for three years, have you?
당신은 3년 동안 연애를 하지 않았죠 ?
I'm too busy to talk to you.
나는 너무 바빠서 당신과 이야기할 수 없습니다.
The more you say that, the more I think it's not about work.
그런 말을 하면 할수록 일에 관한 건 아닌 것 같아요.
It's not appropriate to talk now. We'll talk later.
지금 이야기하는 것은 적절하지 않습니다. 나중에 다시 이야기 해.
Fast. Let's drink.
빠른. 마시자.
Hey!
여기요!
How dare you forget me?
어떻게 감히 나를 잊어?
No, I haven't forgotten. Cheers!
아니요, 잊지 않았습니다. 건배!
That's too weird.
너무 이상해요.
Is he in a relationship?
그 사람이 연애 중인가요?
Guan Ji.
관지.
Let's drink. What do you think?
마시자. 어떻게 생각하나요?
Are you thinking about women?
여자에 대해 생각하고 있나요?
I go first. Have fun.
내가 먼저 간다. 재미있게 보내세요.
- Why are you in a hurry to leave? - Guan Ji.
- 왜 서둘러 떠나나요? - 관지.
Why is he so weird today?
오늘 그 사람 왜 이렇게 이상해?
- What is happening? - Let's see.
- 무슨 일이에요? - 어디 보자.
Is there anything else?
다른 것이 있나요?
Are you busy with work…
일이 바쁘신가요 …
related to Le'an Technology lately?
최근 Le'an Technology와 관련이 있나요 ?
Are you having problems with this?
이것에 문제가 있나요 ?
My colleague is writing a draft for Lieying.
제 동료가 Lieying의 초안을 작성 중입니다.
I also did the same interview with Mr. Chen from Le'an.
나는 또한 Le'an의 Mr. Chen과 같은 인터뷰를 했습니다 .
If I'm right,
내가 옳다면,
there may be different opinions in Yunchuang…
Yunchuang에서는 다른 의견이 있을 수 있습니다 …
against Lieying and Le'an.
Lieying과 Le'an을 상대로.
Lieying weighed in secretly and openly in an interview…
리에잉은 인터뷰에서 은밀하고 공개적으로 무게를 두었는데 …
that Yunchuang will invest with them,
Yunchuang이 그들과 함께 투자 할 것이라고
and Le'an has expressed the same idea.
Le'an도 같은 생각을 표현했습니다.
But, you said in the last interview that you…
그런데 지난 인터뷰에서 말씀하셨는데...
appreciate technological innovation more...
기술 혁신에 감사드립니다 more...
and core technology autonomy,
핵심 기술 자율성,
so you are more inclined towards Lean Technology.
그래서 당신은 린 기술에 더 관심을 갖게 됩니다 .
But, there may be a different opinion in Yunchuang.
그러나 운창에서는 다른 의견이 있을 수 있다.
If Guan Capital wants to join,
관캐피탈이 합류하고 싶다면,
so their opinion is also very important.
그래서 그들의 의견 도 매우 중요합니다.
So that's why you've been so busy lately.
그래서 최근에 너무 바빴어요.
So?
그래서?
I happened to be doing a personal interview with Chen Kang.
우연히 Chen Kang과 개인 인터뷰를 하게 되었습니다 .
So, I want to use your interview as an opportunity…
그래서 저는 당신의 인터뷰를 기회로 삼고 싶습니다 …
to do an exclusive interview series…
독점 인터뷰 시리즈를 하기 위해 …
before you finish this.
이 일을 끝내기 전에 .
I want to invite some related parties,
관련자를 초대하고 싶은데 ,
such as Yunchuang, Le'an and Guan Capital, in discussion.
Yunchuang, Le'an 및 Guan Capital 과 같은 논의가 진행 중입니다.
what do you want to drink
무엇을 마시고 싶으십니까
Lemon juice, thank you.
레몬즙, 고마워요.
do you want ice?
얼음 먹을래?
Oh my god, you are so handsome.
맙소사, 당신은 너무 잘생겼어요.
What?
무엇?
Son.
아들.
If you are right,
당신이 옳다면,
Why do you think I will succeed?
내가 왜 성공할 것이라고 생각하는가 ?
If I do as you say,
내가 네 말대로 하면 ,
How much headline coverage can you get?
얼마나 많은 헤드라인 보도를 얻을 수 있나요?
There is a girl here.
여기 한 소녀가 있습니다.
Female friend?
여자 친구?
Shi Yan had a female friend?
Shi Yan에게 여자 친구가 있었나요?
Tuan Shi,
투안시,
did i bother you and your girlfriend?
내가 너랑 네 여자친구를 귀찮게 했니 ?
Please consider my suggestions carefully.
제 제안을 주의 깊게 고려해 보시기 바랍니다 .
Female friend?
여자 친구?
The woman in the room,
방에 있던 여자,
isn't she your girlfriend
그 사람 네 여자친구 아니야?
Not.
아니다.
Good, if that's the case.
그렇다면 좋습니다.
Good?
좋은?
What kind of good is that?
그게 무슨 소용이 있나요?
Just…
단지…
We can avoid unnecessary misunderstandings.
불필요한 오해를 피할 수 있습니다 .
Misunderstanding?
오해?
As an example?
예로서?
So, you're saying my nephew won't get it wrong?
그럼 내 조카가 틀리지 않을 거라는 겁니까 ?
Nephew?
조카?
Nephew? That means…
조카? 그 의미는…
It will be worse if your nephew gets it wrong.
조카가 잘못하면 상황 이 더 나빠질 것입니다 .
I go first. Early rest.
내가 먼저 간다. 조기 휴식.
Who's coming?
누가 오나요?
I seem to hear a woman's voice.
여자 목소리가 들리는 것 같아요.
Barely.
간신히.
I almost got into a fight with his nephew.
나는 그의 조카와 거의 싸울 뻔했습니다 .
If I ran into him earlier,
내가 그 사람을 더 일찍 만났더라면,
Yunchuang special report and digital magazine upgrade...
운추특보 및 디지털 매거진 업그레이드…
must end.
끝나야 합니다.
He came here without taking this back.
그는 이것을 돌려받지 않고 여기에 왔습니다.
Interesting trick.
흥미로운 트릭.
What are you looking at?
무엇을 보고 있나요?
Who let you out?
누가 당신을 내보내줬나요?
Who was that person just now?
방금 그 사람은 누구였나요?
Uncle's girlfriend?
삼촌 여자친구?
Uncle, I've thought about it.
삼촌, 생각해 봤어요.
What if I don't go to work for now?
지금 회사에 가지 않으면 어떻게 되나요 ?
Can I go abroad to study?
유학을 갈 수 있나요 ?
Studying abroad?
유학 중이신가요?
You really deserve to say that?
당신은 정말 그런 말을 할 자격이 있나요?
Actually,
실제로,
why do people have to do something meaningless...
왜 사람들은 의미도 없는 일을 해야 하는가 ?
and it doesn't work?
작동하지 않나요?
Our entire family is elite…
우리 가족은 모두 엘리트입니다…
who work hard to earn money.
돈을 벌기 위해 열심히 일하는 사람 .
But, no one…
하지만, 아무도…
there is time to spend money and enjoy life.
돈을 쓰고 인생을 즐길 시간이 있습니다 .
So, why can't I be that person?
그렇다면 나는 왜 그런 사람이 될 수 없는 걸까?
If someone has to spend money,
누군가 돈을 써야 한다면 ,
I can do.
내가 할 수있는.
In high school, you never passed chemistry.
고등학교에서는 화학을 통과한 적이 없습니다.
But, you know more about cosmetic ingredients...
하지만 화장품 성분에 대해서는 당신이 더 많이 알고 있습니다.
from the Chemistry teacher.
화학 선생님으로부터.
You were sent to college abroad,
해외대학으로 보내셨군요 .
and your english is not good,
그리고 네 영어는 좋지 않아.
but that doesn't stop you from booking a ticket…
하지만 그렇다고 해서 티켓 예약이 중단되는 것은 아닙니다 …
and travel around the world.
그리고 전 세계를 여행하세요.
So, this is not something that doesn't work.
따라서 이것은 작동하지 않는 것이 아닙니다 .
It depends on whether you want to succeed or not.
그것은 당신이 성공하고 싶은지 아닌지에 달려 있습니다.
I know I did something wrong.
나는 내가 뭔가 잘못했다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
But, uncle, whatever you want me to do,
하지만 삼촌, 제가 원하는 것은 무엇이든
Uncle can't let me go to work.
삼촌은 내가 회사에 가는 것을 허락 하지 않는다 .
I never wake up early…
난 절대 일찍 일어나지 않아...
and staying up late for college entrance exams.
그리고 대학 입시를 위해 늦게까지 자지 않습니다 .
Should I work…
일을 해야 하나…
nine in the morning to five in the evening for a few thousand salary now?
지금 몇천 월급으로 아침 9시부터 저녁 5시까지 ?
It's almost the end of the year.
이제 곧 연말이 다가오고 있습니다.
Why don't we talk about this after the new year.
새해가 지나면 이것에 대해 이야기하는 것이 어떨까요 ?
Is it okay?
괜찮나요?
- Tolonglah, pak cik. - Qin Shi Yue.
- Tolonglah, pak cik - Qin Shi Yue.
The Shi family does not keep useless people.
Shi 가족은 쓸모없는 사람들을 가두지 않습니다.
Not bad.
나쁘지 않다.
You really have the potential…
당신은 정말로 잠재력을 가지고 있습니다…
to become an expert without a teacher.
선생님 없이 전문가가 되기 위해.
You went there and didn't take the earring back…
거기 가서 귀걸이 도 안 가져갔잖아 …
to see him again.
그를 다시 만나려고.
You create opportunities.
당신은 기회를 만듭니다.
Smart.
똑똑한.
So, you have to contact him immediately...
그러니 그 사람에게 즉시 연락해야 합니다 ...
to arrange a time to go home again.
다시 집에 갈 시간을 정하기 위해 .
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
We'll talk later. I still have something to do here.
나중에 다시 이야기 해. 아직 여기서 할 일이 있어요.
Smart, so to speak.
말하자면 똑똑합니다.
I did n't take it back on purpose.
일부러 다시 가져오지 않았어요 .
But, I don't have the number.
그런데 전화번호가 없어요.
How do I contact him?
그 사람에게 어떻게 연락하나요?
I don't know if the special report will be successful or not.
특집보고가 성공할지는 모르겠습니다 .
Alas!
아아!
What should I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
They all say it's hard to ask you out in person,
다들 직접 만나서 데이트 신청하기 힘들다고 하는데 ,
I didn't think you came out either.
나도 당신이 나온 줄은 몰랐어요.
Want to go out or not...
나갈까 말까...
depends on who the person is.
그 사람이 누구인지에 따라 다릅니다.
It's late.
늦었 어.
Nothing else to see here.
여기서는 더 볼 것이 없습니다 .
So, why don't we go somewhere else?
그럼 우리 다른 곳으로 가는 게 어때요 ?
Tonight is a beautiful night.
오늘밤은 아름다운 밤입니다.
There are also beautiful views elsewhere.
다른 곳에서도 아름다운 풍경이 보입니다 .
Or, should we go get something to drink?
아니면 마실 것 좀 사러 갈까?
Or, you want to…
아니면…
It's time to go somewhere else.
이제 다른 곳으로 갈 시간입니다 .
I really want to go somewhere else.
나는 정말로 다른 곳으로 가고 싶다 .
But, not with you.
하지만 당신과는 그렇지 않아요.
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
Goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.
Tuan Shi.
투안시.
I think my earrings fell in your car.
내 귀걸이가 당신 차에 떨어진 것 같아요 .
Did you see it?
당신은 그것을 볼 않았다?
I don't see.
모르겠어요.
Earrings are very important to me.
귀걸이는 나에게 매우 중요합니다.
Can you search again?
다시 검색할 수 있나요?
How important is it?
얼마나 중요합니까?
Xu Yu Ling was called to the author's office.
Xu Yu Ling은 작가의 사무실로 불려갔습니다 .
Maybe they want to use the draft?
어쩌면 초안을 사용하고 싶어할까요?
I have done everything I should have done.
나는 내가 해야 할 일 을 다 했다 .
Maybe I did what I shouldn't have done too.
어쩌면 나 또한 하지 말아야 할 일을 했을 수도 있다.
I'm still confident in my draft.
나는 아직도 내 초안에 자신이 있다.
Since I've done all I can,
내가 할 수 있는 건 다 했으니 ,
I just leave it to fate.
그냥 운명에 맡기겠습니다.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
I want to wash my face to refresh myself,
세수해서 기분 전환하고 싶은데 ,
and I will be back to continue exploring the value of some news.
그리고 저는 뉴스의 가치를 계속 탐구하기 위해 다시 돌아올 것입니다 .
Regardless, my career still has to go on.
그럼에도 불구하고 내 경력은 계속되어야합니다.
Don't mention it again.
다시는 언급하지 마세요.
Shi Yan was really…
시옌은 정말...
I am very unfortunate.
나는 매우 불행하다.
Shi Yan did not say anything useful at all.
Shi Yan은 전혀 유용한 말을 하지 않았습니다 .
It's all just normal conversation.
다 그냥 일상적인 대화에요.
If he doesn't want to be interviewed, he should just say it.
인터뷰를 원하지 않는다면 그냥 말해야 합니다.
Why did he do that to me?
그 사람이 나한테 왜 그랬어요?
He is really useless.
그는 정말 쓸모가 없습니다.
Just a casual conversation?
그냥 일상적인 대화?
But he gave me a lot of information.
하지만 그는 나에게 많은 정보를 주었다.
Who knows how he dealt with Shi Yan?
그가 Shi Yan을 어떻게 대했는지 누가 알겠습니까 ?
You know that looks really good, right?
정말 좋은 것 아시죠 ?
Besides, he will do anything to achieve his goals.
게다가 그는 자신의 목표를 달성하기 위해 무엇이든 할 것입니다.
I have already interviewed Shi Yan,
이미 Shi Yan과 인터뷰를 한 적이 있습니다.
and he was also able to interview Tang Yi.
그리고 그는 또한 Tang Yi를 인터뷰 할 수 있었습니다 .
Using his draft? He…
그의 초안을 사용한다고? 그…
- Luckily it wasn't damaged. - Thank you.
- 다행히 파손되지는 않았습니다. - 감사합니다.
Thank you for the compliment, Yu Ling.
칭찬 해주셔서 감사합니다 , Yu Ling님.
Enough already.
이미 충분합니다.
Xu Yu Ling did something very unfair this time.
Xu Yu Ling은 이번에 매우 불공평한 일을 했습니다.
I warned him earlier.
나는 그에게 일찍 경고했다.
I will put it on the record.
기록으로 남겨두겠습니다.
He will be judged accordingly…
그는 그에 따라 심판을 받을 것이다…
during performance and year-end evaluation.
성과 및 연말 평가 중.
Next time, I will avoid this kind of situation.
다음에는 이런 상황은 피하겠습니다.
Stealing other people's drafts is not allowed.
다른 사람의 초안을 도용하는 행위 는 허용되지 않습니다.
Is the warning enough?
경고는 충분합니까?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
You want me to fire him?
내가 그 사람을 해고하길 바라나요?
He's just very depressed.
그는 매우 우울합니다.
Our brand has not been launched yet.
우리 브랜드는 아직 런칭되지 않았습니다.
Our financial news coverage is very small.
우리의 금융 뉴스 보도 범위는 매우 작습니다.
It doesn't matter if the company fires him…
회사에서 해고 해도 상관없어요 ...
or he stops himself,
아니면 스스로 멈춰서거나
others will surely ask why.
다른 사람들은 분명히 이유를 물을 것입니다.
His career will also be affected.
그의 경력도 영향을 받을 것이다.
Why don't you say anything?
왜 아무 말도 하지 않나요?
I can understand him stealing my interview,
나는 그가 내 인터뷰를 훔치는 것을 이해합니다 .
but why did he have to steal my interview outline?
그런데 그 사람은 왜 내 인터뷰 개요를 훔쳐야 했던 걸까?
Doesn't this prove that your interview outline is better?
이것은 당신의 면접 개요가 더 낫다는 것을 증명하지 않습니까 ?
He has proven it with his actions…
그는 자신의 행동으로 그것을 증명했다 …
that you are better than him.
당신이 그 사람보다 낫다고.
This time, you have won beautifully.
이번에는 멋지게 승리하셨습니다.
For a journalist, the biggest punishment is...
기자에게 가장 큰 벌은…
thwarted by the journalistic ability of others.
다른 사람들의 저널리즘 능력 으로 인해 좌절되었습니다 .
I think, this time,
제 생각에는 이번에는
he really learned his lesson.
그는 정말로 교훈을 얻었습니다.
Shu Yi.
슈이.
You still have a long way to go in this industry.
아직 이 업계에서 갈 길이 멀다.
Be merciful while you can.
할 수 있을 때 자비를 베푸십시오.
So, Shi Yan chose my interview outline, right?
그래서 Shi Yan이 내 인터뷰 개요를 선택했지요?
Of.
의.
Shi Yan was quite principled.
Shi Yan은 매우 원칙적이었습니다.
This time, he didn't make a fool of the Financial Introduction,
이번에는 금융 소개를 바보로 만들지 않았습니다 .
he did not refuse Xu Yu Ling's interview.
그는 Xu Yu Ling의 인터뷰를 거부하지 않았습니다 .
He also gives you enough information.
그는 또한 당신에게 충분한 정보를 제공합니다.
In the end, nobody loses.
결국 아무도 잃지 않습니다.
Look at his EQ and learn from him.
그의 EQ를 보고 그에게서 배우세요.
There is one more thing. I think you understand it too.
한 가지가 더 있습니다. 당신도 그것을 이해한다고 생각합니다.
Sama ada Yunchuang atau Shi Yan,
Sama ada Yunchuang atau Shi Yan,
they chose Financial Introduction first…
재무 소개를 먼저 선택했는데 …
and then choose one of you two.
그리고 둘 중 하나를 선택하세요.
Sister Yi, I understand.
이 자매님, 이해합니다.
All my achievements are based on our magazine platform,
나의 모든 업적은 우리 매거진 플랫폼을 기반으로 하며,
which is among the best in the industry.
이는 업계 최고 중 하나입니다.
So, I want to write better for each article…
그래서 글마다 더 좋은 글을 쓰고 싶은데 ...
to defend the dignity of Financial Identification.
금융 식별의 존엄성을 보호합니다 .
You are so beautiful and smart,
당신은 너무 아름답고 똑똑해요.
so don't waste your time getting angry.
그러니 화를 내는 데 시간을 낭비하지 마세요 .
Thank you for your compliment, author.
칭찬 해주셔서 감사합니다 , 작가님.
A beautiful and intelligent person is going to interview now.
지금 아름답고 똑똑한 사람이 인터뷰를 하러 갑니다.
Helo?
헬리콥터?
I'm not busy.
나는 바쁘지 않다.
I just had a conversation with a subordinate.
방금 부하 직원과 대화를 나눴습니다 .
He has a strong will,
그 사람은 의지가 강하고,
just like me when I was young.
어렸을 때의 나처럼.
I have arranged it with the HR department.
HR 부서와 협의했습니다 .
There is no problem for him to come and be a trainee.
와서 연습생 생활을 하는 데에는 문제가 없습니다 .
But, whether he would be accepted depended on his abilities.
그러나 그가 받아들여질지는 그의 능력에 달렸다.
Maybe a lot of people…
아마도 많은 사람들이…
think I'm better suited in research than entrepreneurship,
나는 창업보다는 연구에 더 적합하다고 생각해요.
but my mentor always encouraged me…
하지만 제 멘토는 항상 저를 격려해 주셨죠…
to apply what is learned.
배운 것을 적용하는 것 .
What was more important was the country's industrial development.
더 중요한 것은 국가의 산업 발전이었습니다.
So, I have to try it.
그래서 나는 그것을 시도해야합니다.
In the past, everyone still used…
과거에는 모두가 여전히 사용했습니다…
traditional technology to make domestic substitutes for chips.
칩을 국내에서 대체 할 수 있는 전통적인 기술 .
So, I guess…
아마도…
we have to find something new,
새로운 것을 찾아야 해요 .
although there may be some risks.
비록 약간의 위험이 있을 수 있지만.
When we succeed,
우리가 성공했을 때,
Our products will be internationally competitive …
우리 제품은 국제적으로 경쟁력을 갖추게 될 것입니다…
because we do not copy the achievements of others.
왜냐하면 우리는 다른 사람의 성취를 모방하지 않기 때문입니다 .
After listening to your experience, I feel your life,
당신의 경험을 듣고 나면 당신의 삶이 느껴집니다.
up to this point, it is very determined.
지금까지는 매우 단호했습니다.
Have you ever worried or hesitated?
고민하거나 망설인 적 있으신가요?
To be honest, when I first got into this field,
솔직히 말해서 제가 이 분야에 처음 입문했을 때,
and learn this technology,
이 기술을 배우고,
My original intention was to serve the community.
나의 원래 의도는 지역사회에 봉사하는 것이었습니다.
But, recently, I suddenly realized…
그런데 최근 문득 깨달았습니다...
with the current development of Le'an Technology,
현재 Le'an Technology의 발전 과 함께 ,
if I'm still blind...
내가 아직 눈이 멀었다면...
considering the research stage only,
연구단계만 고려하면 ,
regardless of the feelings and opinions of my team members,
팀원들의 감정과 의견과는 상관없이 ,
I am self-important towards them.
나는 그들에 대해 자만심이 있습니다.
Le'an is not just mine.
Le'an은 나만의 것이 아니다.
It is the hard work of our entire team.
그것은 우리 팀 전체의 노력입니다 .
So, if you ask…
그래서 물어보면…
whether I ever worried or hesitated,
내가 걱정한 적도, 망설였던 적도 있지만
now is the moment I worry and hesitate the most.
지금이 가장 고민하고 망설이는 순간이다 .
Tuan Chen,
투안 첸,
even though the things we face are different,
비록 우리가 직면한 상황은 다르지만
but i understand you
하지만 난 당신을 이해해요
Some things may just be you who are diligent in the beginning.
어떤 것들은 처음에는 부지런한 당신 일 수도 있습니다 .
Every step is difficult at this time.
지금은 모든 단계가 어렵습니다.
After that, there are people who persevere together, that's not easy either.
그 후에도 함께 버티는 사람들이 있는데 , 그것도 쉽지 않죠.
But in this era,
하지만 이 시대에는
have an ideal career and practice it…
이상적인 직업을 갖고 그것을 실천하십시오…
has become a very lucky thing.
참 다행스러운 일이 되었습니다 .
I believe as long as you are strong,
당신이 강 하다면 나는 믿습니다 .
the possibilities are unlimited.
가능성은 무한합니다.
Delicious! Very delicious!
맛있는! 아주 맛있는!
Uncle is not only good at business,
삼촌은 사업만 잘하는 게 아니라 ,
but also good at cooking.
하지만 요리도 잘해요.
Uncle Aunt's charm no one can resist.
누구도 거부할 수 없는 삼촌 이모의 매력 .
If you like it, eat more.
맛있다면 더 먹어보세요.
When you're full, you can go.
인원이 다 차면 가셔도 됩니다.
Go? Where to?
가다? 어디로?
Uncle, I suddenly remembered I have an appointment.
삼촌, 갑자기 약속이 생각났어요.
I go first. Eat slowly.
내가 먼저 간다. 천천히 먹어.
Qin Shi Yue,
진시유에,
if you dare to walk out of this door,
만약 네가 감히 이 문 밖으로 나가려고 한다면,
I will deactivate your card immediately.
즉시 귀하의 카드를 비활성화하겠습니다 .
It's okay if the card is deactivated.
카드가 비활성화되어도 괜찮습니다.
I will ask my grandfather for money.
나는 할아버지에게 돈을 달라고 할 것이다.
You can ask your grandfather for money.
할아버지에게 돈을 요구할 수 있습니다 .
But, don't you think of coming back here.
하지만 여기로 다시 올 생각은 하지 마세요.
I will change the password. Think carefully.
비밀번호를 변경하겠습니다. 잘 생각 해봐.
The best uncle, the most caring about me,
나를 가장 걱정해주는 최고의 삼촌 ,
and my dearest
그리고 내 사랑
You won't do this to me, will you?
당신은 나에게 이런 짓을하지 않을 것입니다 , 그렇죠?
My love is deep.
내 사랑은 깊습니다.
That's why I discipline you strictly.
그러므로 내가 너희를 엄히 징계하는 것이니라
How long until I get home?
집에 도착할 때까지 얼마나 걸리나요?
Give me some time…
나에게 시간을 좀 줘…
to adapt to life in China.
중국 생활에 적응하기 위해
Don't act like you're unfamiliar with the environment here.
여기 환경이 익숙하지 않은 것처럼 행동하지 마세요 .
You have traveled all over the world since childhood.
당신은 어린 시절부터 전 세계를 여행했습니다 .
You are used to any environment.
당신은 어떤 환경에도 익숙합니다 .
Uncle,
삼촌,
at least I graduated from a prestigious university.
적어도 나는 명문 대학을 졸업했습니다.
Do you want to sell me just like that?
나를 그렇게 팔고 싶나요 ?
And, for just a few thousand a month?
그리고 한 달에 몇 천 정도?
This is a bad deal.
이것은 나쁜 거래입니다.
You think too highly of yourself, don't you?
당신은 자신을 너무 높이 평가하고 있지 않나요?
A trainer is not worth much.
트레이너는 별로 가치가 없습니다.
If not for money, why do I have to go to work?
돈이 없다면 왜 일하러 가야 합니까?
Our family does not lack money.
우리 가족은 돈이 부족하지 않습니다.
I'm not a problem girl and I don't cause problems either.
나는 문제아 도 아니고 문제를 일으키지도 않습니다.
Isn't that enough?
그거면 충분하지 않아?
Qin Shi Yue.
진시유에.
Work is not just a tool to get money.
일은 단지 돈을 벌기 위한 도구가 아닙니다 .
It also reflects a person's sense of social responsibility…
또한 개인의 사회적 책임감을 반영합니다 …
and personal values.
그리고 개인적인 가치.
If you don't lack anything and have energy to spare,
부족한 것이 없고 여유가 있다면
so why not do something…
그러니 뭔가를 해보는 건 어떨까요…
that means for society and others?
그것은 사회와 다른 사람들을 위한 것입니까?
Any other questions?
다른 질문?
If not, sit down and have breakfast.
그렇지 않다면 앉아서 아침을 먹어라.
After we eat, I'll take you there.
식사 후에 는 제가 그곳으로 데려가겠습니다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Stop the car.
차를 세워.
Good morning. Are you up at night again?
좋은 아침이에요. 또 밤에 일어났어?
I have good news. I just heard that our department…
좋은 소식이있어. 방금 우리 부서가 …
will get two new trainees.
두 명의 새로운 연습생을 얻게 됩니다.
What's so good about it?
무엇이 그렇게 좋은가요?
Of course that's good news. Don't you want to find a coach?
물론 좋은 소식이죠. 코치를 찾고 싶지 않나요?
You are very busy.
당신은 매우 바쁘다.
It would be great if someone worked as your assistant.
누군가가 당신의 조수로 일하면 좋을 것입니다 .
You can also avoid staying awake at night.
밤에 깨어 있는 것도 피할 수 있습니다 .
Don't joke. It's not certain who will help whom.
농담하지 마세요. 누가 누구를 도울지는 확실하지 않습니다 .
You know what he's going to do?
그 사람이 무슨 짓을 할지 아세요?
No, and I don't care.
아니요, 상관없어요.
I heard he got an interview with an important person.
그 사람이 중요한 사람과 인터뷰를 했다고 들었어요 .
I think he will go to the interview.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 면접에 갈 것 같아.
Looks like he's sure to get headline coverage next.
그는 다음번에 헤드라인을 장식할 것으로 보입니다 .
If so, I wish him the best of luck.
그렇다면 그에게 행운이 있기를 바랍니다.
You don't have to worry when he's with me.
그 사람이 나와 함께 있으면 걱정할 필요가 없습니다 .
Although he was a bit late,
조금 늦긴 했지만,
it was still his first day at work. He just needs to adapt.
아직 그의 출근 첫날이었다. 그는 적응하기만 하면 됩니다.
Do not worry.
걱정 하지마.
I work first and we'll talk later.
내가 먼저 일하고 나중에 얘기하자.
This is the new intern we hired for our team. Try to see.
우리 팀에 채용된 신입 인턴입니다 . 보려고 노력하십시오.
We do not need an intern at the moment.
지금은 인턴이 필요하지 않습니다 .
Give it to another team.
다른 팀에 넘겨주세요.
Xu Yu Ling's team already has one.
Xu Yu Ling 팀에는 이미 하나가 있습니다.
This one has been assigned to you.
이것은 당신에게 할당되었습니다.
Lead him.
그를 이끌어라.
Sis Yi, my workload is heavy enough.
이씨, 내 작업량은 충분히 무겁습니다.
I really don't have the time and energy to lead new people.
새로운 사람들을 이끌 시간과 에너지가 정말 없습니다 .
I know your workload is heavy.
당신의 업무량이 과중하다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
That's why I myself found you a helper…
그래서 나는 당신을 도우미로 찾았습니다…
to help you take pictures and organize materials.
사진을 찍고 자료를 정리하는 데 도움이 됩니다 .
Let's be honest here.
여기서 솔직해지자.
What is this trainer's background?
이 트레이너의 배경은 무엇입니까?
All I can tell you is…
내가 말할 수 있는 건…
we hired him after careful consideration.
우리는 신중한 고려 끝에 그를 채용했습니다 .
So, I have to accept it, right?
그럼 받아들여야겠죠?
From a work perspective, this is a training task that I am giving you.
업무 관점에서 볼 때 이것은 제가 여러분에게 제공하는 훈련 과제입니다.
From a more personal perspective,
좀 더 개인적인 관점에서 보면,
consider this as I owe you a favor.
내가 당신에게 은혜를 입었으니 이것을 고려해 주십시오 .
Okay.
좋아요.
Don't worry, author.
걱정하지 마세요, 작가님.
I will lead him well.
내가 그를 잘 이끌겠습니다.
He graduated from a prestigious university with high tuition fees.
그는 등록금이 비싼 명문 대학을 졸업했습니다 .
He is from a rich family.
그는 부유한 집안 출신이다.
Why doesn't he just sit at home?
그 사람은 왜 집에 가만히 앉아 있지 않는 걸까요?
Why did he come here and work in the news industry?
그는 왜 이곳에 와서 뉴스 업계에서 일했는가?
Tolerable, and she's beautiful.
견딜만하고 그녀는 아름답습니다.
Her qualifications are beautiful.
그녀의 자격은 아름답습니다.
He is our junior editor-in-chief.
그는 우리 후배 편집장입니다.
He's an excellent student, isn't he?
그 사람은 정말 훌륭한 학생이잖아요, 그렇죠?
What are you worried about?
당신은 무엇을 걱정합니까?
Look at his grades.
그 사람 성적을 보세요.
His CGPA is just enough to graduate.
그의 CGPA는 졸업하기에 충분합니다 .
Look at his resume. He also included…
그의 이력서를 보세요. 그는 또한 다음을 포함했습니다…
which he is the champion of the campus singing competition.
그는 캠퍼스 노래 대회 의 챔피언입니다 .
Obviously he has nothing to show for it.
분명히 그는 그것에 대해 보여줄 것이 없습니다.
He was just wasted in college.
그는 대학에서 그냥 낭비했습니다.
From her background, you can tell she is a spoiled rich girl.
그녀의 배경을 보면 그녀가 버릇없는 부자임을 알 수 있습니다 .
100% sure.
100% 확실합니다.
The author really treated you "well".
작성자님이 정말 "잘" 대해주셨네요.
He gave you troublemakers.
그는 당신에게 문제를 일으키는 사람을 주셨습니다.
You can't blame him, and you can't make him angry.
그를 비난할 수도 없고 그를 화나게 할 수도 없습니다.